nio.com 2017-10-14

# NIO - Privacy Policy

NEXTEV Official Website: [http://www.nio.io](http://www.nio.io/)

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: November 21, 2016**

NEXTEV LIMITED (“ **NEXTEV** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **our** ” or “ **ours** ”) may collect, store, process and use your personal information for providing, maintaining and improving our service as well as upgrading the service quality and optimizing service functions. Our Privacy Policy covers <http://www.nio.io/> (this “ **Website** ”).

We understand and are committed to protecting all reasonable privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy is meant to explain to you how we collect, store, process and use your personal information. Please do read it carefully. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by emailing at: [comms.us@nio.io](mailto:comms.us@nio.io).

**1\. Method and Scope of Information Collection**

When you use the service of this Website or service provided by us, we may collect, store and use the following information concerning you. If you do not provide such information, you may be unable to enjoy certain services or the intended benefits of relevant services provided by us.

**Information provided by you**

  * Relevant personal information, such as your name, telephone number, email and etc., that you may provide to us when you are registering with us or using our service;
  * The shared information provided by you to other parties through our service and the information stored when you are using our service.

**Your information acquired by us**

We may collect the following information when you are using our service:

Log information. Technical information automatically collected by our system through cookies or other means when you use our service, including:

  * Equipment or software information, such as the configuration information provided by your mobile device, web browser or other programs used to access our service, and the version and identification code of your mobile device;
  * Web browsing information, i.e., the website page you visited, time and duration of your visit and etc;
  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address;

**2\. Cookies**

This Website uses the so-called “cookies”. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer. If you visit a website, the website will use cookies to remember you. They allow us to make your visit to our Website more enjoyable and to tailor the Website to better match your demands. The cookies stored on your computer will remain effective permanently after your first visit to our Website.

You can set your web browser to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. You can also set your browser to reject cookies. However, if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access or use certain functions of this Website.

**3\. Method and Scope of Information Use**

We may use the information collected in the process of providing the service to you for the following purposes:

(1) to provide our services to you;

(2) for identity verification, customer service, archival filing and backup, security protection and other purposes in relation to the provision of the service;

(3) to help us improve the service quality, upgrade service functions and develop new functions;

(4) to provide you with relevant advertisements, promotions and campaigns and evaluate the effectiveness of such advertisements, promotions and campaigns;

(5) to better understand how you access and use our services, for the purposes of trying to respond to customer desires and preferences, including language and location customization, personalized help and instructions, or other responses to your and other customers’ usage of our services;

(6) to allow you to participate in surveys and other activities about our products and services.

**4\. User’s Control of Information**

We will make all efforts possible to take proper technical measures to guarantee your access to, update and modification of the personal information provided by you.

**5\. Links to Other Websites**

The service provided by us may include or link to services provided or operated by third parties (for instance, a third party’s recruitment service page linked to when you click the [recruitment] page). Using of the third party’s service or providing of information to the third party shall be subject to the terms and conditions of the third party’s terms of service and privacy policy, instead of this Privacy Policy.

**_We are not responsible for the content or security of other sites that we link to._**

**6\. Sharing of the Information**

Without your consent, except as stated below, we will not share your personal information with or provide your personal information to third parties:

**_(1) to provide to or share with our affiliated companies, partners, third-party service providers, contractors and agents for the purpose of providing our service to you or for purposes set out in Article 3 (“Method and Scope of Information Use”);_**

(2) to comply with laws and regulations, court order or other legal procedures, or requirements of competent authorities;

(3) within the limits required by law or to the extent permitted by law, to protect the rights, property and safety of ourselves, our employees, users of the service and the public; and

(4) for the needs of transactions such as merger, acquisition or assets sale, in which case your personal information may be transferred by us, provided that before such transfer, appropriate notice will be delivered to you. We will also ensure that after such transfer, your personal information will be equivalently protected as under this Privacy Policy.

**7\. Storage of Information**

Your personal information will be stored on the servers within the territory of mainland China and generally such information will not be transferred abroad,  ** _unless for the purpose of the proceeding Article 3 and Article 6._**

**8\. Update of the Privacy Policy**

If we decide to update our Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on this Website through the web notification prior to the effectiveness of the new Privacy Policy, so that you will know what information has been changed. **_Your continued use of the service will be deemed as acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy.If you do not agree to the updated provisions, you should stop using the service._**

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us [comms.us@nio.io](mailto:comms.us@nio.io)
